# **WILLIAM MUIJS**

### Frontend Developer

+31685129807

Remote

williammuys@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/william-muijs

₾ 05-01-1994



I am an enthusiastic and creative frontend developer with 3+ years of experience at various companies and projects. The most important things in my professional life are continuous improvement of knowledge and quality of work. I have a great passion for designing and developing complex digital environments.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Frontend Developer - Freelance

#### **Itonomy**

08-2021 - 09-2021



Angular code audit for a big player in Dutch e-commerce. Provided an extensive audit report containing info and suggestions for improving their current Angular PWA.

### Frontend Developer

#### Incentro

02-2018 - 08-2021

Utrecht

Web application development with the Alfresco Digital Business Platform with experience at various companies and projects. Alfresco is a content management system used to manage the lifecycle of records/documents from capture through retention to final destruction.

## PROJECTS (VIA INCENTRO)

#### Rijksoverheid

**1** 05-2020 - 07-2021

From scratch implementation of the Alfresco Digital Business Platform with a web application and RESTful microservices.

 Angular 2+, TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, RxJS, Jasmine, Karma, Cypress, Java, Spring, SQL, BPMN, Git and more

#### **APS Group**

04-2020

Built a successful proof-of-concept web application to demo the functionalities of the Alfresco Digital Business Platform.

 Angular 2+, TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, RxJS, BPMN, Git, Trello



### **SKILLS**

Angular	Туре	Script	
JavaScri	pt H	HTML	
CSS	SCSS	RxJS	
NgRx	NPM	Java	
Spring	Cypress		
Jasmine	Karma		

### **EDUCATION**

Master's Degree, **Business Information** Management

**Erasmus University** Rotterdam

**12-2016 - 12-2017** 

Bachelor's Degree, International Business Administration

**University of Twente** 

**12-2012 - 12-2015** 

VWO, Economics and Society

Guido de Brès

**2006 - 2012** 

### STUDY ABROAD

**Honors Business** Administration

Ivev Business School at **Western University** 

#### Gemeente Rotterdam

**12-2018 - 12-2019** 

From scratch implementation of the Alfresco Digital Business Platform with a web application and RESTful microservices.

 Angular 2+, TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, RxJS, Java, Spring, SQL, BPMN, Git and more

### C. Steinweg Group



10-2018 - 11-2018

Worked on a content migration tool for an Alfresco Content Services instance.

· Java, Git

### Saxion University of Applied Sciences



07-2018 - 08-2018

Added features to an existing web application for the (lifecycle) management of school exams using Alfresco Content Services.

· Angular 2+, HTML, TypeScript, CSS, SCSS, RxJS, Git

#### Gemeente Zaanstad



**1** 04-2018 - 06-2018

Implementation of Alfresco Content Services plus the development of custom business logic.

· Java, JavaScript, Git



**7** 09-2017 - 12-2017

Exchange semester in London, Ontario, Canada

### **Business Management** and Administration

Universidad Pablo de Olavide

**1** 09-2014 - 01-2015

Exchange semester in Seville, Spain

### LANGUAGES

Dutch



**English** 



### OTHER

Spanish



#### Sabbaticals

In 2020 I took a 3 month sabbatical during which I traveled in a few countries in South America.

In 2015-2016, between my bachelor's and master's, I worked and traveled in Australia and Southeast Asia for a total of 8 months.